Lis Suthasinee Vesurai

Experienced UX Engineer / Front End Developer with a great eye for design who knows how to write clean, clear, and efficient code. Expert in HTML/CSS. Familiar with vanilla JavaScript, jQuery, and Angular 2+. Well versed in responsive websites, Storybook design system and multiple CMS systems.

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

Netskope, Dec 2015 - May 2020

Translated InVision mockups into functional prototypes/templates/Angular components.

Revamped legacy pages on admin portal, responsible for structuring and writing all LESS/CSS code.

Collaborated with UX designer to build a design system for Angular2 components in Storybook.

Wrote Chrome browser plugin for capturing web traffic in JSON format to be used with Netskope analytics tools.

Wrote Catchpoint test scripts for performance tests.

Front End Developer

Blue Shield of California, Sep 2014 - Oct 2015

Translated graphics mockups into functional prototypes for portal redesign project.

Designed / architected portals, pages and microsites to efficiently deploy content management system features to meet business objectives.

UI Developer

BlackBerry, Aug 2010 - Feb 2014

Worked with the UX team to transform designs into a functional prototype for BlackBerry Developer Portal

Web UI Developer

Cellmania (Acquired by BlackBerry), Nov 2006 - Aug 2010

Delivered more than 150 functional web/xhtml wap storefront prototypes, and minisites for mobile carriers worldwide, including Sprint, Virgin Mobile, Boost, Telstra (Australia), Orange (UK), Tata (India), SingTel, and Optus.

Web Technologist

Network Associates (McAfee), May 1999 - Feb 2004

Built and maintained several corporate websites.

Wrote HTML & CSS style guide and procedures manual for corporate web developers.

SKILLS & TOOLS

HTML5, CSS3, LESS, JavaScript, AngularJS, Angular2, jQuery, D3, Highcharts, Sass, JSON, Bootstrap, Foundation, Storybook, InVision, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, PHP, JSP, ASP, CMS, Tridion, TeamSite, IBM WCM, SVN, Perforce, Git, PhpStorm, MyEclipse, Jira

EDUCATION

Bachelor Degree of Communication Arts, Major of Advertising

Assumption
University Thailand

Class of 1997



Email & Phone

lisvesurai@gmail.com

650.318.1804

Portfolio

www.lis.codes